另外两人的交集在这里
the other two here.
特里·罗杰斯是在这里买的东西
And this is where Terry Rodgers bought his groceries.
看起来保罗·希克斯
It looks like Paul Hicks
见过医生后可能也去了那里
might have gone there after his doctor's appointment.
迪弗和埃拉德的交集附近有什么
Now, what was at the intersection where Deaver and Ellard crossed?
一个购物中心  大约有十几家商铺
That's a shopping center with a dozen or so businesses.
正在查商家信息
We're getting a list right now.
我们的一名副官在城郊
One of our deputies sighted an abandoned car
发现了一辆被遗弃的车辆
on the outskirts of town.
在车尾部还有另外一辆车的轮胎印
There was a second set of tire tracks behind it
和特里·罗杰斯被劫持地点的轮胎印相吻合
that matched those found at Terry Rodgers' abduction site.
车辆登记在谢丽尔·温斯洛名下
Vehicle's registered to Cheryl Winslow,
住址是达文波特街4801号
4801 Davenport Avenue.
都是些婴儿洗礼会上拿到的礼物
These are all from a baby shower.